export const question_Bank = [{
        id : "1",
        question : "What do you call a fake noodle?",
        Ans : "Impasta",
        Ans1 : "Soba"
    }, {
        id : "2",
        question : "Which iconic leader led the Salt March as a part of the Indian independence movement in 1930?",
        Ans : "Mahatma Gandh",
        Ans1 : "Sarojini Naidu"
    }, {
        id : "3",
        question : "What ancient Indian text is a collection of hymns, prayers, and rituals and is considered one of the oldest religious scriptures in the world?",
        Ans : "Yajurveda",
        Ans1 : "The Rigveda"
    }, {
        id : "4",
        question : "What's a vampire's favorite fruit?",
        Ans : "Bloodorange",
        Ans1 : "Boobeans"
    }, {
        id : "5",
        question : "What do you call a fish wearing a crown?",
        Ans : "Barracuda",
        Ans1 : "kingfish"
    }, {
        id : "6",
        question : "What do you call a lawyer who doesn't chase ambulances?",
        Ans : "Retired",
        Ans1 : "Busy"
    }, {
        id : "7",
        question : "What's a criminal's best asset?",
        Ans : "Liebility",
        Ans1 : "honesty"
    }, {
        id : "8",
        question : "What's a lawyer's favorite game?",
        Ans : "Hide & sue",
        Ans1 : "Lawsuit"
    }, {
        id : "9",
        question : "What's a judge's favorite snack?",
        Ans : "Lays",
        Ans1 : "Justice"
    }, {
        id : "10",
        question : "What do you call a lawyer who doesn't chase frivolous lawsuits?",
        Ans : "Retired",
        Ans1 : "Jobless"
    }];
    

    
export const ansCart = [{
    id : "1",
    Ans : "Impasta"
}, {
    id : "2",
    Ans : "Mahatma Gandh"
}, {
    id : "3",
    Ans : "The Rigveda"
}, {
    id : "4",
    Ans : "Bloodorange"
}, {
    id : "5",
    Ans : "kingfish"
}, {
    id : "6",
    Ans : "Retired"
}, {
    id : "7",
    Ans : "Liebility"
}, {
    id : "8",
    Ans : "Lawsuit"
}, {
    id : "9",
    Ans : "Justice"
}, {
    id : "10",
    Ans : "Jobless"
}];